( soft instrumental music )
( ominous suspenseful music )
( thunder crashes )
( creature roars )
( soft eerie music )
( liquid trickling )
( liquid bubbling )
( flames blazing )
- You are being such a good boy .
Would you like some more cereal , sweetheart ?
( boy screams )
( boy grunting )
- [ Man ] He 's really being a monster again today !
( boy screaming )
Trudy , goddamn it , help me !
( platter smashing )
- [ Trudy ] ( groans ) Can 't you be more careful ?
- [ Man ] I 'm doing the best I can !
He 's out of control !
( boy screams ) ( boy growls )
- [ Trudy ] Sit still !
Stop it !
Could you please hold him ?
- [ Man ] Don 't do that . Stop kicking !
- [ Trudy ] Oh , why can 't you be more like your brother ?
( boy gasps ) ( boy grunts )
( boy screams )
Be quiet !
Shut up ! ( boy screams )
( boy growls ) ( boy whines )
( boy screams ) ( intense music )
( music intensifying ) ow !
( hand slaps )
( floors creaking ) ( ominous music )
( soft rock music )
( heavy rock music )
♪ I get all up ♪
♪ Now ♪
♪ Where she sings that it 's over ♪
- Mm . There 's a place in Tribeca for $ 3,000 .
- That 's still too expensive .
All the money I saved up won 't even cover two months ' rent .
I 'm gonna have to work
every second I 'm not in class until graduation .
- Carly , don 't even think about not going .
- I 'm not .
- Good .
Because you know how proud I am of you .
- It 's just an internship .
- At InStyle Magazine .
Or would you rather stay
at the Waffle House as a waitress forever ?
- No , thanks . - Yeah . ( laughs )
- Hey , babe . - Hi .
- Sorry , there were these two drunk rednecks
wrestling in the bathroom .
- Really ?
- There 's no rednecks in New York .
- No . There 's not . ( clears throat )
- You know , I 'm gonna go see what Blake 's doing .
Seems to like that car more than me nowadays .
- Now that we have a second ,
and I 'm not trying to make this a big deal , I swear .
You know I want to have a good time
on our road trip this weekend .
But why on earth did your brother have to come with us ?
I mean , I thought you said your parents weren 't gonna post
his bail anymore .
- They didn 't .
Blake did .
He invited him .
I guess Nick makes him feel more bad-ass , I don 't know .
♪ Board on my helicopter Friday ♪
♪ Wednesday got locked up ♪
♪ Calling the associates up ♪
♪ I need a new velour Monday ♪
- Blake .
♪ They got me in jail that I cop ♪
- What up , Paige ?
♪ More fifth of sea glass ♪
♪ Peep the unique fashions ♪
♪ Street amble , let the heat handle ♪
♪ Smooth , one of the illest fleets ♪
♪ Ice-water vocab , ' bout to take over the streets ♪
♪ Unh , yeah ♪
♪ Now what 's fuckin ' with us ♪
- Fine .
♪ One of the illest fleets ♪
- Baby , come back here .
You know it ain 't like that .
I was messing with the GPS
and I saw a shortcut .
Think it 'll save us an hour .
So we can spend more time ...
( Blake whispering )
( Paige chuckles )
Okay ? - Uh-huh .
- How you doing ? - Hello .
Uh !
Get a job . - What 's up , my man ?
- That 's nice . - Shh .
- Yeah .
- Here you go . ( Nick groans )
( Dalton laughs )
- So what do you think , guys ?
Gonna be a sweet game tomorrow , huh ?
- ( chuckles ) Yeah .
( Dalton speaking gibberish )
- Dalton , please don 't film me .
- What ? - Please ?
- It 's just on . I 'm not filming now .
- The red light 's on . - Hey , come on .
Put the camera down .
You know she doesn 't like having people up in her face .
She folds under pressure .
- Nick , you got something to say to me ?
- No , no , I think you 've already spoken enough
for the both of us , don 't you ?
- You guys are lame . I 'm out of here .
See ya .
- Dalton , put down that damn camera .
( Dalton laughing ) God !
♪ Return to me , return to me , return to me ♪
♪ Leave me no one ♪
♪ Turn to me , return to me , make me turn away ♪
( engine revving )
- [ Announcer ] Record crowds are expected
for college football 's biggest game of the year ...
- It 's gonna be packed tomorrow .
- Really ?
- Dude , speaking of packed ,
my legs are killing me back here , man .
- Don 't worry , man .
It 's not Wade 's fault
his little Hot Wheels car only fits two .
- It 's more like a Shot Wheels car , isn 't it , Wade ?
Wade , what did you do , go to the barber shop and ask
for a He-Man haircut , or what ? ( laughs )
- [ Nick ] Shut up , Dalton .
( both snickering )
- [ Dalton ] Ow , dude .
You hurt me .
- [ Wade ] What the hell is this ?
- Oh , man .
- This sucks .
- So much for his nice little shortcut .
I hope he 's not gonna get us lost .
- Yeah , right . - Yeah .
- Damn , yo !
Yo , wake up ! Wake up , wake up ! ( laughs )
- Oh , my God !
- [ Dalton ] ( laughs ) Look at her licking that guy !
You 're caught on tape !
( horn honking ) - Hello ! Oh , my God !
What are they doing ? !
- [ Nick ] Is she flossing herself with that thing ?
- What are you doing ? - Look at his face !
( cell phone rings ) - She 's calling me .
- She 's blushing ! - You are so busted .
- Lip balm , I dropped my stupid lip balm .
- She dropped her lip balm .
- Yeah . ( Carly laughs )
- Yeah , right , you dropped your lip balm .
( all laughing )
- [ Carly ] So , what 's up ?
- I don 't know . It 's getting late .
What do you want to do ? - Keep going .
We don 't even have tickets .
- Babe , there 's gonna be a million scalpers there .
Besides , if we keep driving , there is no way
I 'm staying up for this game .
- Why don 't we just camp out ?
I mean , we 're close enough , right ?
- Yeah , let 's just pull over here .
Come on . We 'll wake up early .
- Yeah , all right .
- [ Paige ] All right , we 're pulling Over .
- All right . ( horn honks )
- Hey , wax museum .
( ominous music )
- You like that kind of stuff , Wade ?
- Yeah , I don 't know . Sometimes .
- Yeah , I guess if you like things
pretending to be other things ,
which you obviously do .
Right , sis ?
( engine rumbling ) ( rock music )
- [ Paige ] Where are we going , Blake ?
- [ Blake ] I 'm just looking for some privacy .
♪ My best friend 's a butcher , he has 16 knives ! ♪
♪ He carries them all over the town ♪
- Wow . - You like it , right ?
This is great .
- Your car sucks , dude .
( Dalton groans ) - Paige , come with me .
We 'll grab the stuff .
Well ? - I couldn 't .
There 's no point in freaking him out right now .
- As opposed to when you find out you are pregnant ?
- Carly , I 'm not sure , okay ?
- I just think you should have a conversation with him .
- He 's been looking forward to this stupid
football game for months ,
and I don 't want to ruin it for him by starting a fight .
- Paige , he 's not gonna marry you .
His parents won 't let him .
- Who says I want to get married ?
Besides , I 've been late before .
When I know for sure ,
I promise to talk to him , okay ?
Let 's go .
( rock music ) ( light chattering )
- [ Carly ] There are ticks out here .
- [ Dalton ] Yeah , don 't help us or nothing .
- Let 's set up . - Aw , yeah !
- Pass ! Pass !
- Here we go . - You don 't want to ...
Too slow ! Too slow !
( guys yelling )
- Touchdown !
Nice arm .
I see why they gave you a scholarship .
- Yeah , it 's a real tragedy , ain 't it ?
- Yeah , it is .
- Wade ...
Help Dalton , okay ?
Please ?
- Bye , Wade . - Asshole .
- You know what ?
You can be a prick to me , that 's fine ,
but he didn 't do anything to you .
- Hmm . So you admit that you did something .
- I admit according to you I did something . Sure .
- You dimed me out .
- I did not dime you out .
When the sheriffs came to the house
and asked me where you got the car ,
I said I didn 't know .
I didn 't even know it was stolen .
And you 're blaming that on me ?
- You could have covered for me , huh ?
- You get caught for stealing a car and it 's my fault .
You 're resisting arrest and it 's the cop 's fault .
- ( chuckles ) Well , he took a swing at me , you know ?
- Look , get kicked off the football team ,
it 's the coach 's fault .
Mom and Dad kick you out of the house ,
it 's their fault .
You can 't even keep a job for more than two weeks ,
' cause it 's every manager 's fault .
- I 'm surrounded by idiots .
- So why did you come , to piss me off ?
( Nick snickers )
- Don 't you get it ?
You 're the good twin .
I 'm the evil one . ( groans )
- Grow up .
You are so afraid to take things seriously .
- Oh . Yeah .
As afraid as Wade is
of leaving good ol ' Gainesville ? Huh ?
New York City .
Well , I hear they got buildings as tall as the sky !
- Okay .
( ominous music ) - Two , 42 ... Hike !
- Go , go !
Whoa .
What 's that smell ?
- That 's bad .
- Whoa .
- Oh , my God .
- Dalton , did you crap your pants again ?
- Huh ? No .
I don 't know . Maybe .
I mean , I 'm wearing my work clothes , so ...
- Oh !
Ugh , it 's horrible .
- Something 's dead out there .
- No , something 's dead right here .
We need to drink it back to life .
Bless me , dawg .
( energetic music )
- Come on , man .
Hi , pretty Carly .
Hey , what 's Wade short for , dude ? ( chuckles )
Who ?
Ooh .
What up , Nick ?
- Stop !
- [ Dalton ] You guys gonna do it tonight , or what ?
- Screw off , dude . - Stop .
- What ?
Come on , you know you want it .
I was joking . Come on , man , enough !
You don 't got to spray it at me , dude .
Dude , look at that ...
- He keeps messing around , though .
- God , dude .
♪ You call me what you want to ♪
♪ They call me sire ♪
- Dalton , what did I say ?
- All right , my bad , my bad . Sorry .
What ? No , it 's off . - It 's killing me .
Give it ... - No !
- [ Carly ] Oh , when the tables turn !
- Come on . Don 't .
- [ Carly ] Look how cute you are on camera , though !
You look good !
I think we might have to do a little makeover .
What do you think ? - Looks like a Smurf .
- So why 'd you steal that car , anyway ?
I mean , you didn 't need to do that .
Get that rush , huh ?
- Something like that .
- You 're coming out . - No , I don 't know , man .
I don 't know . - If you don 't ,
I will be so mad . ( giggles )
- [ Dalton ] Damn , Paige !
- Look how good you look ! - Hey .
- He looks like Elton John ,
but more gay .
- Elton John is gay ? ( girls giggling )
- You look hot . - Hey , shut up .
- Isn 't yellow his color ? - It 's so in style .
- [ Wade ] Why don 't you ever make me that pretty , Carly ?
- [ Carly ] Hi .
♪ Don 't let go till I can 't breathe ♪
- [ Carly ] Look at you .
- Hi .
- Give me my camera , baby , come on now .
♪ Cut me up ♪
- [ Dalton ] Oh , yeah , that 's good .
Let me get some of that action .
That 's hot .
♪ Cut me up ♪
♪ Cut through me ♪
- Don 't even think about it .
I ain 't kissing you , dude .
- [ Dalton ] Come on , you know you want to , man .
Ha-ha . Just kidding .
Besides , I wouldn 't kiss your ass for shit .
( engine idles )
( ominous music )
- Yeah ?
- Hey , yo , man , you need something ?
- [ Carly ] What does he want ?
- Hey , can you turn off your lights , please ?
( intense music ) ( finger tapping )
- Okay , this is getting kind of creepy .
- Hey , come on , man . Get out of here .
Nothing to see here . Let 's go .
- Can we help you ? - Maybe we 're on his property .
- No , we didn 't pass a gate .
- Hey , man , turn your lights off .
- [ Wade ] Hello !
- Turn your lights off .
I 'm serious , man , turn your lights off
or I 'm whipping someone 's ass .
- It 's all right . It 's cool , man .
( glass shattering )
- Nick !
Oh , my ...
( engine rumbling )
- What ? !
Yeah !
( engine hums )
That was great .
That was great , dude .
- My man Nick here 's hard-core .
- What the hell was that about , huh ?
- [ Dalton ] You 're the man , dude .
- Don 't encourage him .
Come on . He 's gone .
( light tense music )
( footsteps pattering )
( dramatic music )
( footsteps pattering ) ( ominous music )
( music intensifying )
Wade .
Wade ! ( Wade grunts )
I heard something .
( Wade groans )
- It 's probably a serial killer or something .
( soft eerie music )
( crickets chirping )
( animal chittering )
( Carly gasps )
( bird calling )
( crickets chirping )
( soft eerie music )
( dramatic music ) What are you doing ?
- ( gasping ) You scared me .
What are you doing ?
- Getting you back to bed .
Come on . Let 's go to sleep .
- I heard something . - Get in that tent .
( Carly giggles )
- Ah , damn it .
Hey , it 's 2 : 30 ! Get up !
Let 's go , guys . Get up .
Get up !
Wade , Dalton , let 's go .
( clapping ) We 're gonna miss the damn game .
Nick ! Get up !
( sighs ) Damn .
- Dude , you see my camera anywhere ?
- Nah , man .
- You guys seen my camera anywhere ?
- [ Nick ] Like I give a shit about your camera .
( Carly chuckles )
- So , you and Wade talk some more ?
- We 're just in different places right now .
And he hasn 't given me a guilt trip for going ,
so I can 't give him one for staying .
Ugh !
( ominous music )
- Oh , my God , there 's that smell again .
- I think it 's coming from over there . ( grunts )
- Yeah , let 's go follow the smell . ( scoffs )
- What ? I want to see what it is .
- Why ?
- [ Carly ] Come on !
( engine sputtering ) - What the hell was that ?
( Dalton sighs )
No way .
Are you serious ?
It was brand-new .
( Nick chuckles ) Someone 's fucking with me .
- I cannot believe you 're making me do this .
( chuckles ) Only you .
- Come on . It 'll be fine . - I 'm gonna throw up .
( Carly grunts ) ( insects buzzing )
- Oh , my God . I hate you .
( Carly laughs )
( dramatic music ) - Whoa !
- Carly !
( Carly thudding )
( Carly sobs ) ( insects buzzing )
Carly !
- Paige ! Are you okay ?
- [ Carly ] I 'm stuck !
Wade !
Please help me get out of here !
- [ Paige ] We 're down here !
( Carly screams ) Guys , help us !
( Carly whimpers )
( eerie music ) ( Carly gasps )
- Guys !
- Where are you ? ! - Get down here !
- Carly ! - Hey ! Hey !
- I can 't get out ! - Carly , I 'm coming !
- Here ! I 'm here , hey !
- Wade ! Where are you ? - Hang on , baby !
- All right , right here . Carly !
Hold on . I 'm here . - Ah , man .
- Here . Grab me , baby .
Come on . Come on .
I got you . Get up .
Oh .
You all right ?
Oh , man .
- [ Blake ] There 's a roadkill pit down here .
- You all right ? - I fell in .
- Oh , yeah . That smells about right .
- Baby , you okay ? - Uh-huh .
- Come on , I got you .
( Carly panting )
It 's okay .
- [ Blake ] Hey , is that the truck from last night ?
- Not unless he fixed his headlight .
( engine rumbling )
( tools clattering )
( fly buzzing )
- [ Wade ] Hey !
- Don 't you see that ?
What is that ?
( eerie music )
- No way .
What are you doing , man ?
- Anyone need a hand ?
( laughing ) I 'm just foolin ' .
It 's not real , see ?
( finger tapping )
- [ Carly ] ( sighing ) God .
- I found it on the side of the road a few weeks ago .
- Oh , my God , are you okay ?
- Sorry we took so long . - It 's all right .
- What are you guys doing ' round here ?
- We were all camping up through those trees .
- I have water in here somewhere . God .
- Oh , good . - Hey , you guys seen
my camera , by any chance ?
- Are you kidding ?
- No .
- Damn .
- Hey , you don 't know if there 's
a gas station around here , do you ?
- Well , I got some gas in the truck , if -
- I need a fan belt .
- What ?
- Just busted .
- Of course . Perfect .
- Bo might have one .
Runs a station in Ambrose .
- Where 's that ?
- 15 miles up the road .
- Let 's just get one in Baton Rouge .
We 'll put it on when we get back .
- Man , there 's no way I 'm leaving my car .
What if that guy from last night
comes and strips it or something ?
- Well , whatever , man . You 're gonna miss the game , then .
- Yeah , well , that 's not why I came .
- All right , then , look .
I 'll run you up to the station , but let 's go now .
Kickoff 's in a couple hours .
- Dude , you 're already late .
You still gotta find a scalper and snag tickets .
Y 'all should just go now . I 'll stay with my car .
It 's fine . Just go and get me a fan belt on the way back .
And make sure it 's a 15-inch .
Gotcha . - I 'll give you a ride .
- You serious ?
- If you like .
- Well , yeah .
- That 's cool ? - Yeah , if it 's cool .
- I 'm going with you . - No , no , no .
- Carly , no . - Yes . It 'll be fine .
- All right , let 's go .
Come on , Paige .
- Carly .
- What ?
- [ Blake ] Hey , I 'll get you guys tickets
and leave them at will call .
- Thank you .
- All right . All good , man .
- [ Blake ] Come on , babe .
( tense music )
( man chuckles )
- No , it 's okay .
( Carly pants )
- Come on , babe .
So let 's get out of here .
( Dalton exhales )
- Man ,
you 're just gonna let them leave like that ?
With a guy who throws roadkill in a pit for a living ?
- You clean shit for a living , Mr. Septic Tank Man .
What 's the difference ?
- Well , I don 't walk through it , that 's one .
That 's a difference , right ?
Yup . ( chuckles )
( ominous music )
( engine humming ) ( tools clattering )
( man snickers )
- Can you roll the window down , please ?
- [ Wade ] Yeah .
- Sorry ' bout that .
( chuckling ) Truck 's seen better days .
- Do you mind rolling down your window , then ?
- Not at all .
( handle squeaking )
Sorry . I kinda get used to the smell .
- Really ? I don 't think I could ever get used to it .
- Well , you can get used to anything ,
if you 're around it long enough .
Oh , if you get ' em in the early morning
before the sun bakes ' em up , they 're not so bad .
If they 're fresh , though , I just take ' em home .
Why waste the meat ?
( Carly sighs )
- Are we almost there yet ?
- It 's just up the road .
Yep , Ambrose used to be a pretty nice town
before the interstate came in .
You like knives !
- Not really . - Tools of the trade .
You want to see it ? - That 's okay .
- It 's a bowie .
It 's a good knife .
That 'll cut through anything .
( dramatic music )
( tires squealing ) - Oh , shit .
Hey , what 's going on , man ?
You said there was a town up here .
- Well , yeah , there is .
It 's just around that bend .
I gotta flip my hubs into four-wheel .
You mind giving me a hand ?
- When 's the last time that you were here ?
- ( chuckles ) Well , you don 't believe me ?
I forgot this way in 's washed out , that 's all .
- We 'll walk the rest of the way , then .
Thank you . You 've done enough .
- Now , why would you want to do that ?
- Look , we want to walk , okay ? Just let us out now .
- Sure .
( eerie music )
( music intensifying )
Well , get out , then !
Try and do something nice for someone .
- Look , man , it 's not like that , all right ?
We appreciate it .
- ( laughing ) Yeah , I can tell .
- Is he still staring ?
- Yeah . Just keep walking .
- Oh , like I 'm gonna stop .
- Damn ...
Now I feel like a real asshole .
- I don 't care . That guy was a freak .
- Yeah .
( ominous music )
( horns honking )
- Dude , it 's over .
- It 'll move .
( rock song plays low on stereo )
( Blake sighs )
- It 's not moving .
- Look , we 'll make it for the second half .
- Okay , dude , I 'm not sitting in this traffic .
- Well , then what do you want me to do ?
- Come on , man . Let 's just go to Carly and Wade -
- We have to go back come on . - Turn around .
- I 'm not missing the best game of the year .
- Turn the car around . Okay ?
- Come on , they 're waiting for us already .
( horn honks )
- Slow down , speedy . God ! ( Carly laughs )
Miss Ambrose .
Wonder how many teeth you have to have to win that one .
( Carly chuckles )
This is kind of nice . - Yeah .
Oh , wait , babe , there 's a pet store .
- Oh , great . - Come on .
( Carly gasps )
- Are those puppies ? Oh , my God !
Look at them !
- [ Wade ] They 're cute , adorable .
Maybe next time . Come on . - Oh , my God .
- Come on .
( rock music playing softly )
- Hello ?
( Carly sighs )
( bell jangling )
- [ Wade ] Hello ?
( bluesy rock music plays in distance )
You see anybody ? - No , nobody .
( cell phone rings )
- Oh .
Hello ? - Hey , it 's me .
We 're heading back . - Really , why ? What happened ?
- [ Paige ] Traffic .
Did you get that fan belt thing or whatever ?
- ( sighs ) No . There 's no one at the gas station .
I don 't know where we 're going right now .
- [ Paige ] So , where do you want us to pick you up ?
- Why don 't you just head up the road
that we got off at for the campsite ?
It 's washed out at the end .
Call us when you get there . We 'll meet you .
( newscast plays low in background )
- [ Paige ] We 'll camp in the same place as yesterday ,
but , you know , away from that pet cemetery .
- ( chuckles ) Cool . See you then .
- Hey . There 's that House of Wax .
- Wade , what about the fan belt ?
- Well , there 's no one at the station .
- Why don 't we ask someone in the church ?
- All right . All right .
( pipe organ music )
( dog barking in distance )
- [ Priest ] Let us all bow our heads
and say a prayer for our beloved deceased friend .
( mourner sobbing )
- Oh ...
We should go . - Yeah .
( door creaking )
( Wade coughs ) - What do we do ?
Just wait out here ?
- I don 't know .
I feel kind of messed up waiting outside a church
for a funeral to end .
Hey , man , sorry about walking in . We didn 't know -
- You shouldn 't have walked in .
- Yeah , I know , it 's just that we have car trouble
and we 're not from this town .
- We were actually looking for a guy named Bo .
He works at the gas station .
- [ Bo ] You found him .
- Really ?
Well ( clears throat ) ,
we need a fan belt .
We were camping up the road and -
- A fan belt ? - Yeah .
- You walk in on a funeral for a fucking fan belt ?
Well , let me just go dump the casket in the ground .
I 'll be right there .
- Look , we 're sorry .
- Yeah .
( door creaks )
- That 's twice today . I 'm an asshole .
Let 's just go back to the road .
- Hey .
Hey , I 'm sorry .
You know , someone very special to me passed ,
and I didn 't mean to take it out on you .
- No , no , no , no . It 's totally understandable .
- I reckon things will wrap up soon .
Why don 't I meet you guys back at the station
in about a half ?
- That 'd be great , if that 's okay .
- Yeah .
Great .
What ?
- Nothing .
Looks like your fan club 's gotten a little bigger .
- Are you serious ?
- Yeah . I am serious .
And it 's obvious Dalton still has a crush on you , too .
- Oh , my God .
Okay , that 's three times today .
You 're an asshole .
Let 's go see your famous House of Wax .
- [ Wade ] But I 'm still your favorite asshole , right ?
- [ Carly ] Always . ( laughs )
( woman singing in foreign language )
( classical opera music )
I don 't know what you expect to see in here .
( Wade chuckles )
- It is wax .
Like , literally .
- Huh .
( door thuds )
- You 're not gonna go in there , are you ?
- Yeah .
( woman singing in foreign language )
( door thudding )
- [ Carly ] Doesn 't closed mean I don 't want you in here ?
- [ Wade ] Relax , I just want to take a quick look .
- [ Carly ] What if someone 's here ?
- [ Wade ] Hello ? Anyone in here ?
See ? We 're fine .
Wow . How cool is this ?
Everything in here is wax : the floor , the walls .
Look at this . This is wax .
- [ Carly Yeah , cool . Awesome .
- [ Wade ] Who are these people supposed to be ?
- I don 't know .
- Aren 't there supposed to be famous people in a wax museum ?
I don 't recognize this guy . ( chuckles )
- " Trudy opens House of Wax . "
" Trudy 's wax carvings are a hit at the State Fair . " "
" Trudy and husband are expecting first child . "
Since when is a wax sculptor a celebrity ?
- I don 't know . Small town , I guess .
- That 's right . You like small towns .
- I didn 't say I wasn 't gonna like New York .
I just said I haven 't made a decision yet .
I still have time , all right ?
- Mm-hmm .
Well , I 'd really like you to be there with me .
- Oh , no ! There 's a fire .
Help me , Carly . I 'm melting .
My skirt 's gonna catch on fire .
My legs are all burned .
- Cut it out , please . - You 're my hero .
- [ Carly ] That 's not cool .
- Hey , Car .
There 's a dog for you .
Hey , puppy . You a little wax dog , too ?
What up , dawg ?
( dog growling ) Jesus !
( Carly laughs )
- That is cool . - What the ?
Yeah , ha-ha , laugh it up .
What 's a dog doing in here anyway ?
( striking keys )
( light piano music )
- Vincent ?
Another Vincent .
( eerie music )
This Vincent guy 's quite the artist .
- Yeah , I think this Vincent guy needs therapy .
I mean , look how detailed this is .
Tell me this doesn 't look real .
- I don 't really care .
I mean , not that it 's bad ,
but everything made out of wax ,
don 't you think that 's a little weird ?
- Those aren 't wax .
- Oh , whatever .
Hey , when do you think the last person was here ?
A while , probably .
( dramatic music ) ( Carly gasps )
What ? What is it ?
- I just saw someone .
- It was probably just a wax thing .
- No , no . It wasn 't a wax thing .
It was moving and it was freaky-looking .
- I 'll go check it out .
- Wade , where are you going ?
Don 't leave me .
Wade , come on . - Hang here a second .
- No . Wait .
( door thudding )
( low ominous music )
( door rattling )
( floor creaking )
( distant thudding ) ( dramatic music )
( Carly gasps )
( Carly screams )
( intense music )
- Whoa ! Hey !
Damn , Carly , what 's wrong ?
- This place is freaking me out .
- Hey , calm down . There 's no one out here .
- Please , I just want to go .
- Okay , okay .
We 'll go to the station then .
- [ Dalton ] Ah , dude , I had to pee so bad , man .
( Dalton moaning )
Come on , dude !
- Hey , are you guys gonna have sex ?
- What ? - ' Cause me and Paige are .
- So you two go pick them up .
- Yeah , all right .
- Hey , Paige .
- Yeah ? - Nick and Dalton
are gonna go get them .
- Why ? We can go . - Oh , baby ! Come on .
I 'm tired of driving . - Okay .
- Why don 't you let my man drive ?
- Really ?
Ah , you heard him . Move .
- Give me the damn keys . - Okay , okay , okay .
Very slow . Thank you .
- I still don 't think this is cool ,
just coming in here like this .
- What ?
Look , the door was unlocked .
He said he was gonna be half an hour .
He 's been , like , 45 minutes .
I 'm sure he won 't mind .
You know , if your brother and his yes-man
hadn 't come along in the first place ,
we all would have fit with Blake
and none of this would have happened .
- Once again , that 's not my fault .
- I mean , I don 't understand his beef with me .
I 've always tried to be cool with him .
- Nick 's got beef with everybody .
You just can 't take it personally .
- Yeah , I guess .
- Nick and I always used to stick together ,
and then , when we were in junior high ,
Nick would get into a little trouble here and there
and our parents would always , like , compare us .
I was the good twin ,
and Nick was the evil twin , as he likes to say .
He kind of got this image .
He totally played it up
as if that 's what he had to be or something .
( sighs ) It 's already getting dark .
I hate the winter .
- He 's got everything but a 15-inch .
Just have to use a 16-inch .
Make it work somehow .
- You plan on stealing that ?
- No .
We just didn 't know how much longer you were gonna be ,
and , you know , we didn 't want to interrupt again .
But I left you some money on the counter ,
but you don 't even really have the right size .
You don 't have any 15-inches .
- I do at the house .
- Look , I hope you 're not getting
the wrong idea that we 're in here .
- No , it 's okay .
- Does that cover it ?
- It 's close enough .
Look , why don 't we head up to the house
and get the one you need ?
You know , it 's only a couple blocks .
- Yeah , all right .
- You keep fan belts at your house ?
- Well , I get things delivered there when I 'm not here .
Now , look , if you want to hold onto
the 16 , that 's fine by me .
- No , no , no , no , no , no . It 's okay .
- Hey , you mind if I use your restroom real fast ?
- Oh , up at the house . That one 's out of order .
- All right .
So is it too late
to sign Carly up for that beauty pageant ?
Now , unfortunately , it is ,
' cause you would have won hands down .
- ( chuckles ) Thank you .
- [ Wade ] So , that House of Wax was pretty cool .
- You went inside ? - Yeah .
- Yeah , it was unlocked , so , you know .
- Everything seems to be unlocked around you , now don 't it ?
Yeah , people used to come to see it from miles away .
And Trudy was the main , I guess artist
is the appropriate word .
- What about Vincent ?
I saw his name on a lot of the work .
- One of Trudy 's boys .
- They still around ? - No , no .
It 's a horrible story .
Trudy 's husband , Doc Sinclair ,
he was a doctor in the big city
until he got his license revoked
for doing surgeries on the side , you know ,
stuff that , you know , most doctors wouldn 't dare do .
So , he moved him and Trudy out here to Ambrose ,
made a fresh start with his medical practice
and , you know , Trudy really found
her calling with that whole wax sculpture thing .
It was her dream to do something really incredible here .
Then she had a couple kids , picket fence ...
- What 's so horrible about that ?
- Yeah ?
- Trudy got a cyst in her brain .
She just started rotting away .
Couldn 't work no more ,
and she went crazy .
Things got so bad that Doc Sinclair
finally had to strap her to the bed .
I mean , the whole town could hear her
screaming from the house .
Dr. Sinclair was so depressed that he couldn 't save her ,
he ( mimics gun firing ) blew his head right off .
- That 's terrible .
- It was worse for the two boys ,
left all alone like that .
Both ended up in foster homes .
- Hey , why don 't you two hop in ?
I 'll go get the fan belt ,
and I 'll give you a ride back to your car .
- No , actually , we got some friends picking us up
where the road 's washed out .
- I 'll give you a lift there , then .
It 's the least I could do for making y 'all wait .
- Cool .
- All right .
- Hey , you need ,
you said you need to use the facilities , right ?
- Yeah . Thanks .
- Need to use the can ?
- No , that 's okay . I 'm fine .
All right .
So , where you heading to , anyway ?
- Oh , we 're just going to a football game .
- Hey , the bathroom is right down the hall .
Let me get out of this jacket and tie
and I 'll grab the fan belt . - Okay . Thanks .
( ominous music )
( engine humming )
- Just let me drive , bitch .
He gave me the keys , man .
- Yeah , ' cause he thinks I 'm the one
who stole the car and crashed it .
- Whatever , man .
You didn 't have to cover for me , dude .
- Hey , your jacket 's clean , all right ?
Mine 's already got plenty of stains on it .
One more 's not gonna make a difference .
Where the hell is this place ?
Town 's not even on the GPS .
- That 's weird .
( toilet flushing )
( door creaking )
( soft ominous music )
( Wade squeaks ) ( Wade chuckles )
( Carly sighs deeply )
( keys jingling )
( radio music )
( Carly sighs )
( soft ominous music )
( machine whirring )
( tool rattling )
( tense music )
( music intensifying )
( dramatic music )
( horn honking )
( eerie music )
( ominous music )
( object rattling )
( knocking on door )
- Hello ?
( switch clicking )
Hello ?
( door rattling )
( knocking on door )
Hello ?
( knocking on door ) I 'm in here !
( intense music )
Hello ? I 'm in here !
( knocking on door )
( door rattling )
( knocking on door ) Hey !
( door rattling ) Hello ?
( pounding on door ) Hello !
( skin tearing ) ( Wade screaming )
( intense music )
( Wade whimpering )
( Wade gasping )
( intense music )
( scissors whooshing ) ( Wade screaming )
( horn honking )
( music intensifying )
( foot thudding )
( keypad beeping )
( line ringing )
- Come on .
( phone ringing ) ( rap music playing on radio )
( Paige gasps )
- [ Blake ] Hey , it 's Blake . You know what to do .
( machine beeps )
- Guys , where the hell are you ?
Listen , remember the truck
that came to the campsite last night ?
I think we just ran into him .
( tense music )
Where 's Wade ?
- Oh , he 's not out here ?
Guess he 's still in the bathroom , then .
I got the fan belt .
You 're not in a hurry , are you ?
' Cause I wanted to load the truck up with some stuff first .
What are you doing ?
- Waiting for Wade .
- Open the damn door .
This is my truck .
( handle jiggling ) Hey .
What is the matter with you ?
If you don 't open this door , I 'm gonna call the cops .
- You 're the guy from the campsite .
( hand thudding ) ( Carly shrieks )
( glass shattering ) Wade !
( Carly screams ) - What are you doing ? Stop !
- Wade ! - Get out of the truck !
( Carly grunting )
I 'm just trying to help you .
Give me the keys ! Hey !
( engine starts ) Hey !
Stop or I 'm calling the cops !
( engine revving )
( Carly grunting )
( Carly panting )
( engine revving )
( tires sputtering )
( engine backfiring )
( Carly whimpering )
( ominous music )
( dramatic music ) ( Carly gasps )
- So , you think Carly and Wade are gonna stay together
when she moves to New York ?
' Cause she be looking at me sometimes like ...
- Dalton , it ain 't happening .
- What ? What do you mean ?
- And even if it was happening , it ain 't happening .
Nothing personal .
- Why , you like me better than Wade , right ?
- Wade 's not so bad .
- Yeah , I like Wade , too .
( intense music )
( Carly panting )
( sinister music )
( tool clicking )
( Wade groaning )
( dog whimpering )
( ade grunting )
( Carly panting )
( electrical whirring )
( Wade whimpering weakly )
( machine whirring )
( liquid sputtering )
( Wade muffled screaming )
( sinister music )
( Carly gasping )
( pipe organ playing in distance )
- Help ! Please , somebody !
Please !
Please help me !
( panting ) No !
( people crying )
( eerie music )
( gasps ) No way .
No .
( pipe organ music playing on recording )
Oh , no .
What ...
( mannequin cracking ) ( Carly screams )
( suspenseful music )
( Carly gasps )
No !
( door creaking )
( ominous music )
- [ Bo ] I 'm sorry , Mama .
These people just have no respect .
( eerie music )
( tense music )
( Carly screaming ) ( dramatic music )
( Carly whimpering )
Shh , shh , shh , shh , shh .
- Help ! Help , please !
Please help !
Please ! Over here !
- Shh , shh , shh , shh , shh . - Help me !
- Shh .
- What are you gonna do to me ?
( engine humming )
- Is this it ?
- Yeah .
- Well , should we drive through it , you think ?
- ( scoffs ) Through all that ?
- I don 't know . I could do it .
- Ha !
That 's what I thought .
( car alarm chirps )
- Put me down !
No !
( Carly sobbing )
♪ You cut off ♪
♪ All of your fingers ♪
♪ Trade them in for dollar bills ♪
♪ Cake on some more makeup to cover up all those lines ♪
♪ Wake up and stop shaking ♪
♪ ' Cause you 're just wasting time ... ♪
- [ Carly ] Let me go !
♪ You take but cannot be given ♪
( Carly screams )
♪ You ride but cannot be ridden ♪
- Please .
♪ Pinch this tiny heart of mine ♪
♪ Wrap it up in soiled twine ♪
♪ You never read what you 've written ♪
- [ Nick ] Hello ?
♪ I 'll be your lover ♪
♪ I 'll be forever ♪
- [ Dalton ] Carly ? Wade ?
Hello !
- Dalton !
♪ When I 'm high ♪
- All right , listen .
One word , and this is going through your throat .
Yeah ? - Mm-hmm .
- Man , there 's music playing ,
but I don 't think anyone 's here .
- No one 's here .
- [ Dalton ] Where you going ?
- [ Nick ] To that grocery store we passed .
I 'm thirsty .
- Well , what about your sister and Wade , man ?
- Maybe they 're at the store .
What ?
- Well , I don 't know , man . I mean , we came all this way .
You don 't think we should just look for " em ?
- All right , check it . I 'm gonna go this way .
All right ? You go that way .
We don 't find ' em , we meet back here , go back to the road .
Cool ?
- Okay .
( light music )
- Yo ! Paying customer !
( knocking on door )
Hello !
( dog barking in distance )
( eerie music )
- [ Bo ] Don 't move .
- Now what are you do - - Shh . It 's okay .
( Carly sobbing )
Shh . Just stay still .
( Carly grunting )
It 's a shame we have to close that pretty mouth of yours .
( Carly muffled crying )
Especially with the way those lips curve .
( Carly muffled screaming )
( handle rattling )
- Hey .
I 'm looking for my sister and her boyfriend .
They were looking for a fan belt or something .
( Carly muffled screaming ) ( metal clangs )
- I don 't think I 've seen them .
- Well , this is the only gas station in town , right ?
- That 's right .
- Yeah , then they were definitely here .
- I just told you I didn 't see ' em .
- Does somebody else work here ?
- No , I own the station ,
and I would 've seen them .
- Well ...
I was just here a few minutes ago ,
and you didn 't see me .
You weren 't even here .
- Sorry . Can 't help you .
( Carly muffled cries )
- What was that ?
- Nothing . That was just my dog .
Actually , you know what ?
My brother Vincent was down here for a while .
He could 've helped your sister out .
They could be up at the house .
- No , my friend went that way earlier .
- Really ?
Well , maybe he ran into my brother up there , then .
( music intensifying )
( bone snapping ) ( Carly muffled screaming )
Want to head up to the house ?
- Yeah , whatever .
( Carly muffled sobbing )
- So , what 's your sister look like , anyway ?
- Nick !
Nick , help me !
( dramatic music ) ( Bo grunts )
( fists thudding )
Please help me ! I 'm down here !
( lock clicking )
( door thudding )
( tense music )
Nick !
- Carly !
- [ Carly ] I 'm downstairs !
( door thudding )
( gasps ) Thank God . - Jesus .
Okay . I 'm here , I got you .
- ( grunts ) Okay .
Here . Watch my finger .
Watch my finger .
- Oh , my God .
He did this to you ?
- Where is he ?
Where is he ?
- I locked him out .
Where the hell 's Wade ?
- I don 't know . He went into the house .
This place is a freak show .
Aah !
( intense music )
- Hello ?
Hello ? Anyone here ?
Carly ! Wade !
Hello ?
( Dalton whistles )
Anyone here ?
This is a weird place .
Hello ?
Anyone home ?
Carly .
Carly ?
Wade !
What the hell you doing , bro ?
Man , come on , everyone 's waiting for you at the campsite .
Wade ?
( Wade grunts )
Holy shit , man .
Hold tight , man . Hold tight .
I 'm gonna get you out of this .
Ugh !
Oh , oh !
All right , I 'm sorry , man , I 'm sorry .
Oh , my God .
All right , all right . What happened to you , man ?
Holy ...
( Dalton grunts ) ( dramatic music )
Hold on ! Hold on ! ( Dalton thudding )
( intense music )
No , no !
( knives thudding )
( intense music )
( Carly panting )
( engine rumbling )
- He 's leaving .
All right , stay here .
- Okay .
- Yeah .
All right .
Car 's by the road .
Damn it . Dalton 's got the keys .
Dalton .
Oh , we got to call the cops .
( phone beeping )
Shit .
Hey .
Where 's your cell phone ?
It might be in the truck , up near the house .
- Okay . - What about Wade ?
I think he has him , too . What if he turns him to wax ?
- What do you mean , wax ?
- You don 't get it .
They 're all wax . Everyone .
No , wait .
There was a woman in here .
She was alive . She pulled the curtain back .
( static hissing quietly )
( dramatic music ) ( Nick shouts )
( machine squeaking )
The whole town is rigged .
- That 's impossible .
( mechanism sliding )
You 're saying that that 's a real person ...
Underneath ?
- Yes . At the church , they were all like that .
At least 20 more .
( light ominous music )
♪ Now we 're dancin ' on the floor ♪
♪ With all these players keeping score ♪
♪ But I 'm just tr yin ' to dig your soul ♪
♪ Soul ♪
- [ Blake ] Come here , baby .
♪ Somehow you 're doin ' what you can ♪
♪ To keep a brother holdin ' on ♪
♪ The way you move your body , babe ♪
♪ It drives me wild ♪
♪ I love the way you 're lookin " , babe ♪
♪ You 're just my style ♪
♪ Sexy , and you don 't even know it , baby ♪
♪ You got it open , baby ♪
♪ Like what you do , the way you 're doin ' me ♪
♪ Yeah , yeah , yeah , yeah , yeah ♪
♪ Go on , get down ♪
♪ Get funky , babe ♪
♪ Keep on doin ' what you 're doin ' ♪
♪ What you do ♪
♪ All my players sing ♪
♪ The way you move your body , babe ♪
♪ It drives me wild ♪
♪ I love the way you 're lookin ' , babe ♪
♪ You 're just my style ♪
♪ Sexy , and you don 't even know it , baby ♪
♪ You got it open , baby ♪
- Come here , sexy .
♪ The way you 're doin ' me ♪
- Baby , we need to talk . - Mm-hmm .
- I really need to talk to you .
- What 's up with the music ?
What ?
- ( sighs ) Okay , I 'm not sure ,
and I don 't want to freak you out or anything -
- Wait , baby , just hold on one second ;
I 'm gonna be right back . - I need to tell you this .
- I 'm just gonna go handle the music ; I 'll be right back .
No , let me just tell you this .
Blake ...
Goddamn it ! I need to talk to you for a minute !
Blake !
♪ The way you move your body , babe ♪
♪ It drives me wild ♪
♪ I love the way you 're looking , babe ♪
♪ You 're just my style ... ♪
- [ Carly ] Guys , where the hell are you ?
Listen , remember the truck that came
to the campsite last night ?
I think we just ran into him .
Where 's Wade ?
- [ Bo ] He 's still in the bathroom .
What are you doing ?
- [ Carly ] Waiting for Wade .
- [ Bo ] This is my truck !
- [ Carly ] You 're the guy from the campsite !
( Carly screams ) ( glass shattering )
( wind whistling softly )
- Blake ?
Blake ?
( dramatic music ) ( Paige screams )
( Paige screaming )
( blood sloshing )
( sinister music )
( Paige gasping ) ( switches clicking )
( tense music )
( metal creaking )
( Paige screaming )
( dramatic music )
( Paige breathing heavily )
( ominous music )
( music intensifying )
( door thudding ) ( Paige yelling )
( ominous music )
( Paige gasping )
( glass shattering )
( blood trickling ) ( ominous music )
( reel clicking )
( dog barking in distance )
( suspenseful music )
- He said he had a brother , right ?
- Yeah .
- Vincent .
- At the House of Wax , he did all the sculptures .
He 's got to be the one that does the wax .
What if he 's around here somewhere ?
- [ Nick ] Yeah .
- Wait .
Nick , what are you doing ?
You gotta be careful .
- I am being careful .
( door rattles )
- No , no , no , no , no . It 'll make too much noise .
Why do you have to be so damn stubborn ?
He will find us .
- Yeah , chances are he will , anyway .
At least with this , he might not want to find us .
( glass shattering )
That 's about right .
( dog barks in distance )
( ominous music )
( gun firing )
- Go , Carly . Run . ( intense music )
( soundtrack winding up to speed )
( piano plays somber melody )
J ; I 've written a letter to Daddy
( suspenseful music )
( door creaks ) ( suspenseful music )
♪ Above ♪
♪ I 've written , Dear Daddy , we miss you ♪
- [ Bo ] I know you 're in here .
♪ With us to love ♪
- [ Usher ] Shh .
♪ Instead of a stamp , I 've put kisses ♪
♪ The postman says that 's best to do ♪
♪ I 've written a letter to Daddy ♪
( indistinct chattering ) ( coughing over speaker )
♪ Saying I ♪
( man coughs )
♪ Love you ♪
( piano plays somber melody )
( suspenseful music )
( gun thudding )
- Nick ! ( gun firing )
( Bo grunts )
( Bo grunting )
♪ I love you ♪
( gun firing )
- Edwin , you certainly can play , can 't you ?
- And you certainly can sing .
- Oh !
( Bo grunts )
( arrow shoots ) ( Bo yells )
- Empty shells . ( shells clattering )
Check him for ammo .
( Carly pants )
( suspenseful music )
- There 's nothing in his pockets .
Give me this .
Nick , let 's get out of here .
Let 's go .
- [ Nick ] Is there anybody left alive in this town ?
- [ Carly ] What about this Vincent guy ?
- [ Nick ] Who knows if there even is a Vincent ?
We gotta get out of this place .
- Look , what about Wade and Dalton ?
We can 't just leave them behind .
- [ Nick ] You said your cell phone 's in the truck , right ?
- Yeah .
- All right , this is what we 're gonna do .
I 'm gonna go up to the truck
and get your cell phone ,
and see if I can get some help .
You go back to the road .
Paige and Blake are back - - No way . No .
- Hey . - I 'm not leaving you .
- Why do you have to be so ...
Damn stubborn .
Okay .
We stick together ,
nothing 's gonna happen to us .
- Yeah .
- [ Nick ] Come on .
- That way .
It 's under the front seat .
- Nice parking job .
It 's not in there .
- Wade and Dalton .
- [ Carly ] Wade went in there and never came out .
- All right .
We 'll go in quick , one pass .
If we can 't find them ,
we have to get the hell out of here .
- Yeah .
- Let 's try the back .
( dog barking in distance )
( suspenseful music )
Stay close .
( latch opening )
( door creaks )
( Carly pants )
( phone beeping )
( door creaks )
Dalton ?
Wade ?
- Nick .
Nick , there 's guns .
( suspenseful music )
( glass shatters )
( chains rattling )
It 's bolted to the wall .
( Nick grunts )
There 's got to be a key around here somewhere .
( paper rustles )
( suspenseful music )
( door thudding )
( Bo clattering )
( Bo grunting )
( Bo panting softly )
( water running )
( Bo grunting )
( Bo yells )
( intense music )
- Fuck !
( Bo yells )
( soft music )
( Bo grunting )
( Bo retching )
( Bo panting )
( engine humming )
( brakes squealing )
- No .
( dog barks ) ( Carly panting )
Goddamn it .
I told him not to do that .
Hey !
You don 't ever leave here without me .
You know better than that .
Don 't be so stupid .
What 's the matter with you ?
( Carly panting softly )
Don 't .
I said don 't !
Get .
Get !
Fuckin ' freak .
( match sizzling )
Hey .
Town 's looking real good .
We almost finished what Mama started .
Those two are good . They 'll fit perfect .
( Bo panting )
What 'd I tell you , huh ?
Isn 't your work more real now ?
Ma would be proud .
Yeah , she 'd be real proud .
She always said that your talent would make up
for what God took away from you .
And there 's two more .
We still got a lot of work to do .
( Bo exhales )
Huh ?
( suspenseful music )
( intense music )
( Carly muffled gasp ) - Shh , shh , shh .
It 's okay , okay , okay .
- [ Carly ] I saw Paige and Blake 's bodies .
They 're dead .
- [ Nick ] We got to go . Now .
( generator rumbling )
- [ Carly ] Damn !
- I can 't see anything .
There 's got to be a light here somewhere .
( switches clicking )
( dogs whimpering )
( generator whirring )
( bell ringing )
( dramatic music )
( generator whirring )
Come on .
( suspenseful music )
Dalton .
- Nick .
- ( sighs ) I 'll get you out of there .
( neck snapping ) ( dramatic music )
- No ...
No !
Nick .
Nick , please .
( Carly sobbing )
Oh , no .
( dramatic music )
That 's Vincent !
( Nick grunts )
( blade scrapes )
( Carly grunts )
( Carly yells )
( flames blazing )
( Nick grunts )
- Come on , Carly !
Move it ! Move it !
( Carly whimpers )
( liquid splashing )
( flames whooshing )
- Nick ! Let 's get out of here !
Hurry !
( Carly panting )
- [ Nick ] Come on ! Come this way !
( Carly gasping )
( gasps ) No .
Oh , my God . Wade .
- Come on . - No !
- You sick fuck !
( Bo grunting )
( fists thudding )
( bat thudding ) ( fist thudding )
( flames blazing )
( Nick and Bo grunting )
- [ Bo ] You 're finished .
- No . ( grunts )
( Bo grunting )
( Bo yelling )
( flames blazing )
( Nick shouts )
( Nick yells ) ( Nick grunts )
( bat thudding ) ( Bo grunting )
( flame whooshing )
- Carly ! Behind you !
( Carly panting )
Come on !
Get up ! Please !
( Vincent howling )
( intense music ) - Run !
Go , Carly ! Run !
Hey , Vincent .
Hey !
Vincent !
( Carly gasps )
I swear to God , if you hurt her !
Vincent !
( Nick groaning )
( Carly panting )
( Nick grunting )
( Carly yells )
( sinister music )
( doors sloshing )
( light bulb shatters ) ( Carly pants )
- No ! Listen to me !
Listen to me .
I heard you talking .
You don 't need to do this .
You don 't have to listen to your brother .
I saw Bo 's scars .
And the highchairs !
No ! ( screams )
You 're not a freak !
He was !
( chandelier shattering )
( building shuddering )
( Nick grunting )
You don 't need to do this !
Please !
You 're an artist .
Bo was lying to you . He used you !
Do you really think that your mother
would 've wanted you to do this ?
Please don 't kill me !
( dramatic music ) ( Carly screams )
- Motherfucker !
( Carly thudding )
( both grunting )
Oh , shit .
( intense music ) ( Vincent growling )
Carly !
( Carly grunting )
- I 'm here .
( Carly grunts ) ( Nick yells )
( Vincent growls )
( Carly screams )
- Carly , do it ! Do it now !
( Carly yells ) ( Vincent groaning )
( dramatic music )
( Carly screams )
( Carly grunts )
- Come on !
Nick , get up ! ( both grunting )
( intense music )
( both gasping )
We 're almost there !
- [ Nick ] How do we get out ?
( building shuddering )
( fire blazing )
- Watch out ! - Shit !
- Nick . The wall .
Dig ! ( Nick grunts )
- [ Nick ] Faster ! Faster !
( fire whooshing )
- [ Carly ] Dig !
- Come on , Carly ! Faster !
Go ! Go !
Come on ! ( intense music )
Come on !
- [ Carly ] Oh , God !
( building shuddering )
( Carly gasps )
( building rumbling )
( explosion booming )
( solemn music )
( indistinct radio chattering ) ( sirens wailing in distance )
- Hey , that 's my friend 's camera .
Hey , that 's my friend 's camera !
- Sorry , son , that 's evidence .
You guys okay ? ( Nick laughs )
Well , don 't worry . We 'll get you to the hospital .
- How could no one have known about all of this ?
- Truth is , this town 's hard as hell to get to .
It 's been abandoned 10 years ,
ever since that sugar mill shut down .
Hell , it ain 't even on the map anymore .
We found all those cars in that old factory .
Those Sinclair boys
have been pulling people off the interstate for years .
If it wasn 't for all the smoke from the fire ,
we wouldn 't have even known .
- [ Woman ] Excuse me , sir , Louis wants
to talk to you over here . - Yeah . Excuse me .
( solemn music )
( eerie music ) ( liquid trickling )
- [ Nick ] Maybe there 's some good memories on this .
- You took it ?
- It just felt wrong leaving it behind .
You know ?
- You okay ?
- We 're okay .
- [ Deputy ] Sheriff ?
- Yeah , Dave ?
- [ Dave ] Ran the Sinclair family through CDIC .
Trudy and the doctor didn 't have two sons .
They had three .
( ominous music )
( sinister music )
♪ Burning on ♪
♪ Just like a match you strike to incinerate ♪
♪ The lives ♪
♪ Of everyone you know ♪
♪ And what 's the worst you take ♪
♪ From every heart you break ♪
♪ And like the blade you stain ♪
♪ Well , I 've been holdin ' on tonight ♪
♪ What 's the worst that I can say ♪
♪ Things are better if I stay ♪
♪ So long and good night ♪
♪ Came a time ♪
♪ When every star fall brought you to tears again ♪
♪ We are ♪
♪ The very hurt you sold ♪
♪ And what 's the worst you take ♪
♪ From every heart you break ♪
♪ And like the blade you stain ♪
♪ Well , I 've been holdin ' on tonight ♪
♪ What 's the worst that I can say ♪
♪ Things are better if I stay ♪
♪ So long and good night ♪
♪ Well , if you carry on this way ♪
♪ Things are better if I stay ♪
♪ So long and good night ♪
♪ Can you ♪
♪ Hear me ♪
♪ Are you ♪
♪ Near me ♪
♪ Can we pretend ♪
♪ To leave and then ♪
♪ We 'll meet again ♪
♪ When both our cars collide ♪
♪ What 's the worst that I can say ♪
♪ Things are better if I stay ♪
♪ So long and good night ♪
♪ Well , if you carry on this way ♪
♪ Things are better if I stay ♪
♪ So long and good night ♪
( mellow rock music )
♪ A change of speed ♪
♪ A change of style ♪
♪ A change of scene ♪
♪ With no regrets ♪
♪ A chance to watch ♪
♪ Admire the distance ♪
♪ Still occupied ♪
♪ Though you forget ♪
♪ Different colors , different shades ♪
♪ Over each mistakes were made ♪
♪ I took the blame ♪
( metal rock music )
♪ You desecrate your temple with anger ♪
♪ A hollow body fueled by hate ♪
♪ Feel no better ♪
♪ Anger ♪
♪ Don 't look for answers ♪
♪ Hatred ♪
♪ Blown away , there 's never a reason why ♪
♪ It 's sick either way ♪
♪ Sick either way you ♪
♪ Sick either way you look at it ♪
♪ So take ♪
♪ What you want and leave a hole inside ♪
♪ Take everything you need to keep you satisfied ♪
♪ Break everything you seem to try to hide ♪
♪ Take it all , but you 're never taking me alive ♪
♪ Alive ♪